{
    "meat": [
        {
            "question": "Watch out where the huskies go",
            "choices": ["And don't you eat that yellow snow", "But shouldn't you already know", "Could you really believe that"],
            "answer": "And don't you eat that yellow snow"
        },
        {
            "question": "Call any vegetable",
            "choices": ["Call it never, ew", "Call it by name", "Call it all the time"],
            "answer": "Call it by name"
        },
        {
            "question": "Girl, you thought he was a man",
            "choices": ["And he was", "But he wasn't", "But he was a muffin"],
            "answer": "But he was a muffin"
        },
        {
            "question": "Studebaker",
            "choices": ["Avanti", "Hawk", "Lark"],
            "answer": "Hawk"
        },
        {
            "question": "The crux of the biscuit",
            "choices": ["is the end", "is the apostrophe", "is delicious"],
            "answer": "is the apostrophe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Great",
            "choices": ["Scott!", "Moogly Googly!", "Googly Moogly!"],
            "answer": "Googly Moogly!"
        },
        {
            "question": "I might be movin' to Montana soon, Just to raise me up a crop of",
            "choices": ["Dental Floss", "Toothpaste", "Mouthwash"],
            "answer": "Dental Floss"
        },
        {
            "question": "Help, I'm a",
            "choices": ["Rock", "Paper", "Scissors"],
            "answer": "Rock"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said for a nominal service charge",
            "choices": ["I could reach nirvana tonight", "I could be royal tonight", "I could get home tonight"],
            "answer": "I could reach nirvana tonight"
        },
        {
            "question": "The adventures of",
            "choices": ["George Pearcy!", "Greggery Peccary!", "Glenn Penn!"],
            "answer": "Greggery Peccary!"
        }
    ]
}